[Music]
Welcome back to grow in Grace with KC
and if this is your first time in this
page what we are discussing is
money issues career and
life dreams and in this particular video of
course what we are talking about is
about life insurance and what are the
pros and cons or the difference between term
insurance versus permanent insurance and
again the job of a financial
Planner is to help you assess
what is the perfect or my
policy for you and that is why
also I am explaining to you the
difference between term and permanent
insurance that means
The premium is not the same for all
clients because that is why you can
choose permanent insurance You can
also choose term insurance and this is
what this video is all about all right
so one of the pros no or the difference
between term insurance and permanent insurance
Is that it is lower premium the
premium of term insurance is lower Why is the
insurance coverage only for a certain period so for
example you choose a one year
term or 5 years or 10 years that is all
you will cover your insurance After
that nothing  that you will receive
benefits or you will not have a policy
like that unless you renew so
the premium is lower so permanent
insurance Okay and then it is better here
Is that it is simple to understand This is
your coverage this is the um this is the
some assured you or
your benefits will be available when you die or
something bad happens to you like
accident or
disability So that's it at that period
of time You are covered And that's as
Simple as that okay and also ah it's up to
you no how long you Until
when you want to be covered so
you can Ren next year and then and if
you want to be covered for the next 5
years or for the next 10 years It's up
to you but within that the term you chose that's what
you also need
to pay for to have your
insurance so the cons of term
insurance is that
You only have a certain period of time to cover and then
since um it's only short term
it doesn't have a Cas value it doesn't have a savings
component and so what is the
benefit that's the only thing
you can benefit from your
insurance if you don't  What happened to you
within those coverage period
So you don't get anything because that's
praise the Lord nothing happened SAO '
because that's for protection for
unexpected bad things to happen to you no So
that's just
until your benefits So it does
n't have additional bonuses It doesn't have a
cash value like that Okay while the
permanent insurance is lifetime
coverage So it's long-term
So
while or as long as
you pay your premium you are covered
while you are still alive there is also
permanent insurance that has investment Not all permanent insurance has investment
that's our next video
about vul and traditional insurance so
not all permanent insurance has
investment but That's one of the possible
consol if you choose Permanent
vul is you have cash value
you can take a loan in case of
emergency there is a savings component
Of course um since it's long-term
it's more expensive its premium is more expensive
no it's also a bit complex to understand
Because most of these permanent
insurances have many add-ons many
additional features so it's a bit difficult to
understand and also
its
application is a bit complicated because it's long-term  he so there is
a little more to
process and pass unlike
the one which is one year term
insurance is You can buy it
online and you can check the link below
if you are interested to know how much um
the cheapest insurance
that you can buy no y so example
of term insurance in fwd is set for
tomorrow so the set for tomorrow
can be 5 5 years can be 10 years or
can be up to 55 years old 60 or 65
years old and then his
death benefit is 100% and 100 100% also if
you have a terminal illness no it is
covered there in 42 major critical
illness Okay and then he has child
protection 100% Just in case
you and your spouse die
together from the same cause of death and
then You can also have
a funeral benefit in the set for tomorrow but um
im ma-muscle
is set for life No you can grow your
fund you can you have investment no um
it can grow your investment It depends
on the fund performance Not held by  The
insurance company itself will be the
performance of the funds in the
market, so in case you have a
vul, your risk appetite is what you want so
let's talk about that in our next videos
Okay so there will be more so
I will have videos about each
um design policy and How if that is
right for you allright So that's all the difference
for this video the difference between the
term insurance and permanent insurance
Okay so check my Facebook page if you
have questions and so you can stay
updated about future updates and if
you have um you can Uh watch other
videos of course um Stay tuned for
our next videos no so that
more people can watch our
videos more understand
things about insurance so that
people don't dance too much
insurance really
helps people And that's
the goal of growing chis with KC to
educate more people about insurance and
all the things about our
money, career and dreams in
life no so that together we will
grow and we will all be
blessed by  Thank you for
your attention to this
[Music]